Hi! I'm

Oleksii Donin

Digital Banner Ad Developer; Motion Design; Motion Graphics;

HARD SKILLS

SOFTWARE

Google Web Designer

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe After Effects

Figma

Adobe Animate

Banner ads production	
Motion design	
Web / digital design	
Front end developmetn	

ABOUT ME

I'm a professional digital designer/ developer from Ukraine with more than fifteen years of digital experience. My main specialization is banner ads development. I can create Rich Media ads and HTML5, AMP HTML, and GIF animated standard banner ads. I also have strong motion design, web/digital design, and front-end web development skills.

EDUCATION

Creative Practice (2021 — 2022)

- Web Design Basics
- Design Basics
- Figma Basics
- After Effects Basics

Priazovskiy State Technical

University (2003 — 2008)

 Automation of technological processes and manufactures

% +38 096 3 838 460 ☑ oleksii.donin@gmail.com

Kiev, Ukraine

10th march 1986

- oleksiidonin.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/oleksii-donin/
- behance.net/oleksiidonin

EXPERIENCE

10.2008 — till now

Freelance digital designer/developer

worked as freelancer with Ukrainian branches of Publicis, Universal McCann, Philip Morris International, Havas Group, Mediacom, Twiga Ukraine, BBDO and many others.

05.2008 — 10.2008

Handmade Interactive Ltd

Front-end web developer

03.2007 — 04.2008

Mariupolcity Ltd

Adobe Flash developer

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian	_	_	_	_	_	_
English	_	_	_	_	_	_
Russian						

CODING

Adobe Illustrator

HTML5	
AMPHTML	
CSS3	
JavaScript	
Action Script 3	

SOFT SKILLS

- Time management
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem-solving
- Creativity
- Openness to criticism
- Critical thinking
- Resourcefulness

INTERESTS

- Travel
- Ecotourism
- Modern art
- Design
- Architecture